Finding Aid for the ABC Television Network Scripts and Production Files PASC.0220
UCLA Library Special Collections
ABC Television Network scripts and production files
1954-1974
UCLA Library Special Collections
ABC Television Network
PASC.0220
7.5 Linear Feet (16 boxes)
Collection consists of materials related to the production, promotion and/or programming activities of television shows aired on the American Broadcasting Company from approximately 1954-1974.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift, 1980.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9944358623606533
Scope and Content
The collection consists of materials related to the production, promotion and/or programming activities of television shows aired by the American Broadcasting Company (ABC). The materials appear to have belonged to offices handling promotion and/or programming procedures at the network as described by Harold (Hal) Garb, a correspondent in the files. (Garb was not personally acquainted with the Walt Disney Production files, most of which date previous to his arrival.) The bulk of the collection dates from the 1956-1959 and 1962-1974. Included are scripts, programming and/or promotional information, and production information from a variety of television shows, such as Griff (1973-1974), The Streets of San Francisco (1972-1973), and Walt Disney Productions such as The Mickey Mouse Club (1954-1959). The production,cprograming, and promotional material may include network memos, cast sheets, shooting schedules, story outlines, photo shoot orders, development reports and biographical sketches. Additionally there is script material, including a script written by Rod Serling, for a series titled The New People (1968).
Walt Disney Productions files appear to have been generated by Walt Disney Productions and copied to the network. It is not clear what office at ABC (if any) these files came from. They form a self-contained unit of materials exclusively associated with Disney television productions, which happen to have aired on ABC.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
ABC TV Programing Files
ABC TV Promotional Files
Scripts and Production files
Walt Disney Productions
Television production and direction -- Archives.; Television scripts.; ABC Television Network
- Series 1. ABC TV Programing Files, (Boxes 1-15); (boxes)
  Scope and Contents note
  The ABC TV Programing Files include schedules, credit sheets, programing information, and development reports for television programs aired on ABC. Programming includes Movie of the Week, Mod Squad, Love American Style, Streets of San Francisco, and Griff among others. The series is arranged by television series title.
  - Movie of the Week
    - Development Reports 1971-72 Season, 29 Jan 1971 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Development Reports 1971-72 Season, 12 Mar 1971 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Development Reports 1971-72 Season, 15 Jan 1971 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Development Reports 1971-72 Season, 12 Mar 1971 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Development Reports 1971-72 Season, 5 Mar 1971 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Development Reports 1971-72 Season, 26 Feb 1971 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Development Reports 1971-72 Season, 5 Feb 1971 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Development Reports 1971-72 Season, 12 Feb 1971 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Development Reports 1971-72 Season, 22 Jan 1971 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Development Reports 1971-72 Season, 9 Apr 1971 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Development Reports 1971-72 Season, 2 Jul 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Development Reports 1971-72 Season, 19 Feb 1971 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Development Reports 1971-72 Season, 7 May 1971 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Development Reports 1971-72 Season, 22 Jan 1971 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Development Reports 1971-72 Season, 23 Apr 1971 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Development Reports 1971-72 Season, 15 Jan 1971 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Development Reports 1971-72 Season, 16 Apr 1971 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Development Reports 1971-72 Season, 29 Mar 1971 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Development Reports 1971-72 Season, 2 Apr 1971 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Programming information and dubbing schedules, 1970-71 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Programming information and shooting schedules, 1970-71 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Programming information and sponsor confirmation sheet, 1970-71 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Repeats, 1971-72 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 11 Jan 1971 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 18 Jan 1971 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 5 Apr 1971 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 26 Mar 1971 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 22 Mar 1971 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 30 Dec 1970 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 22 Feb 1971 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 1 Feb 1971 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 17 Sep 1970 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 15 Mar 1971 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 16 Feb 1971 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 9 Mar 1971 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 8 Feb 1971 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 1 Mar 1971 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 26 Oct 1970 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 19 Jul 1971 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 1 Sep 1970 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 21 Jun 1971 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 22 Sep 1970 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 25 Jan 1971 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 6 Oct 1970 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 12 Oct 1970 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 6 Jul 1971 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 27 Jul 1971 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 24 Dec 1970 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 20 Oct 1970 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 2 Nov 1970 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 6 Nov 1970 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 14 Jun 1971 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 14 May 1971 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 7 May 1971 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 17 Nov 1970 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 23 Nov 1970 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 1 Dec 1970 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 17 Dec 1970 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 4 May 1971 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 29 Apr 1971 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Schedule 1970-71 Season, 27 Jul 1971 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Assault on the Wayne
      - broadcast schedule, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Brian's Song
      - Remembering Brian's Song = Brian's Song: development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - But I Don't Want to Get Married
      - broadcast schedule, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Call Her Mom
      - Just Call Me Mom = Call Her Mom: development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Congratulations, It's a Boy
      - development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 5, Folder 4)
        Scope and Content
        Original title: So Is Your Old Man
    - Crowhaven Farm
      - dubbing schedule, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - broadcast schedule, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Deadly Dream
      - development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Death of Me Yet
      - development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Do Not Fold, Spindle or Mutilate
      - development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Dr. Cook's Garden
      - broadcast schedule, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Escape
      - broadcast schedule, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Feminist and the Fuzz
      - broadcast schedule, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Five Desperate Women
      - development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Forgotten Man
      - development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 5, Folder 4)
    - Getting Away From It All
      - development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Gidget
      - Gidget Gets Married: development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Gidget Grows Up: broadcast schedule, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Hound of the Baskervilles
      - development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - House That Wouldn't Die
      - dubbing schedule, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - broadcast schedule, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - How Awful About Allan
      - dubbing schedule, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - broadcast schedule, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - If Tomorrow Comes
      - Glass Hammer = If Tomorrow Comes: development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - In Broad Daylight
      - development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - In Search of America
      - broadcast schedule, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Incident in San Francisco
      - cast list, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - shooting schedule, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Journey of Robert F. Kennedy
      - broadcast schedule, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Last Child
      - development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Longstreet
      - broadcast schedule, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Love Hate Love
      - broadcast schedule, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Madame Sin
      - development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Man Who Wanted To Live Forever
      - broadcast schedule, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Maybe I'll Come Home in the Spring
      - broadcast schedule, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Mr. & Mrs. Bo Jo Jones
      - development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Night Slaves
      - broadcast schedule, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Night Stalker
      - Kolchak Papers = The Night Stalker: development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Old Man Who Cried Wolf
      - broadcast schedule, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Over the Hill Gang Rides Again
      - broadcast schedule, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - People
      - development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Point
      - broadcast schedule, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Reluctant Heroes
      - Egghead on Hill 656 = Reluctant Heroes: development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - River of Gold
      - dubbing schedule, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - broadcast schedule, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Rolling Man
      - development report, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Run, Simon Run
      - broadcast schedule, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Screaming Woman
      - Screaming Women = Screaming Woman: development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Second Chance
      - development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Sheriff
      - broadcast schedule, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Silent Force
      - dubbing schedule, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 3, Box-folder 10 3)
    - Suddenly Single
      - development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Sweet, Sweet Rachel
      - development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Taste of Evil
      - development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Trackers
      - development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Tribes
      - Tribes = Tribe: broadcast schedule, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Two For the Money
      - development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Two On a Bench
      - Siamese Twins = Two On a Bench: development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Weekend of Terror
      - broadcast schedule, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Wild Women
      - dubbing schedule, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - broadcast schedule, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Women in Chains
      - development report, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Yuma
      - dubbing schedule, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - broadcast schedule, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Griff
    - memos, publicity, cast sheet, shooting schedules, 1973 (Box 10)
  - Love American Style
    - Episode 1 - credit sheets, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Episode 10 - credit sheets, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Episode 11 - credit sheets, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Episode 12 - credit sheets, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Episode 13 - credit sheets, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Episode 14 - credit sheets, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Episode 15 - credit sheets, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Episode 16 - credit sheets, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Episode 17 - credit sheets, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Episode 18 - credit sheets, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Episode 19 - credit sheets, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Episode 2 - credit sheets, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Episode 20 - credit sheets, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Episode 21 - credit sheets, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Episode 22 - credit sheets, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Episode 23 - credit sheets, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      General note
      With pilot credits for "Barefoot in the Park."
    - Episode 24 - credit sheets, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Episode 3 - credit sheets, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Episode 4 - credit sheets, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Episode 5 - credit sheets, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Episode 6 - credit sheets, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Episode 7 - credit sheets, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Episode 8 - credit sheets, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Episode 9 - credit sheets, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Love American Style - Daytime
    - General Correspondence, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Timing sheets (1 of 2), 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Timing sheets (2 of 2), 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Love on a Rooftop
    - General correspondence and programming information, 1966-71 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - General correspondence and programming information, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Marcus Welby, M.D.
    - Cast lists - programming information and cast lists, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Preemptions - programming information, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Repeats - programming information, 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Shooting schedules and programming information, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Universal format - programming information, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Matt Lincoln
    - Cast lists and programing information, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - General correspondence and programming information, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Preemptions - programming information, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Universal format - programming information, 1969-70 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Mod Squad
    - 'A' is For Annie - cast lists, Jun 19-29 1970 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Activist (The) - cast lists, Aug 18-26 1970 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Bummer for R.J. (A) - cast lists, Nov 1970 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Comeback (The) - cast lists, Jan 1971 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Credit sheets and programing information, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Double for Danger - cast lists, Nov 1970 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Far Away Place (A) - cast lists, Jul 9-17 1970 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Fever - cast lists, Sep 28-Oct 6 1970 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Hot Hot Car (The) - cast lists, Nov-Dec 1970 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Is That Justice, No, It's The Law - cast lists, Dec 1970 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Is There Anyone Left in Santa Paula? - cast lists, Oct 16-26 1970 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Judas Trap (The) - cast lists, Oct 7-15 1970 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Just Ring The Bell Once - cast lists, Aug 7-17 1970 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Kicks, Inc. - cast lists, Oct-Nov 1970 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Kicks, Inc. - revised cast lists, Oct-Nov 1970 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Long Road Home (The) - cast lists, May 21-29, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Long Road Home (The) - cast lists, May 21-29 1970 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Preemptions, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Price of Love (The) - casts lists, Feb 1971 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Repeats, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Search And Destroy - cast lists, Jun1-9, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - See The Eagles Dying - cast lists, Jun 30-Jul 8 1970 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Shooting schedules and programing information (1 of 4), 1970-71 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Shooting schedules and programing information (2 of 4), 1970 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Shooting schedules and programing information (3 of 4), 1970 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Shooting schedules and programing information (4 of 4), 1970 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Song of Willie (The) - cast lists, Jul 29-Aug 6 1970 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Suffer, Little Children - cast lists, Sep 8-16 1970 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Time of Hyacinths (A) - cast lists, Sep 17-25 1970 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - We Spy - cast lists, Jan-Feb 1971 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Welcome to Our City - cast lists, Jan 15-25 1971 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Welcome to The Human Race, Levi Frazee - cast lists, Jul 22-28 1970 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Who Are The Keepers, Who Are The Inmates? - cast lists, Jun 10-18 1970 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Monday Night Movie
    - General correspondence, programming information, schedules, and film titles, 1970-71 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Programming information and schedules, 1970-71 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Money Maker
    - Call Sheets, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Most Deadly Game (The)
    - Breakdown - cast lists, Aug 28-Sep 4 1970 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - 'I', Said The Sparrow - cast lists, Aug 10-17, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Lady From Praha - cast lists, Sep 14-22 1970 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Little David - cast lists, Aug 19-27, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Preemptions, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Programing information type correspondence, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Programming information and cast lists, 1970-71 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Programming information and dubbing schedules, 1970-71 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - dubbing schedule, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - War Games - cast lists, Jul 21-29, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Who Killed Kindness - cast lists, Sep 23-Oct1 1970 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Witches' Sabbath - cast lists, Jul 30-Aug 7, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Motor House
    - General correspondence, 1970-71 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Murdocks and the McClays (The)
    - General correspondence, 1970-71 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - correspondence, memo, budget, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Nanny and the Professor (The)
    - Preemptions, 1970-71 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Programming information and cast list, 1970-71 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Programming information and credit sheets, 1970-71 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Programming information and shooting schedules, 1970-71 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - cast sheets, memos, shooting schedules, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
    - Repeats, 1970-71 (Box 10, Folder 66)
- Series 2. ABC TV Promotional Files, 1964-1969; (Boxes 6, 7, 15, 16)
  The bulk of the ABC TV Promotional Files include photo routing cards and a small amount of correspondence. The files are arranged by project title.
- Series 3. Scripts and Production files, Late 1950s, late 1960s and 1973; (Boxes 10-15)
  Scripts and Production files consists of script material, outlines, and a small amount of production information. Programing includes Griff and Streets of San Francisco, among others. The series is arranged by television series title.
  - Buffalo Soldiers (The)
    - Buffalo Soldiers (The) - annotated outline with notes, 18 Oct 1968 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      Writers: Peeples, Samuel A.
    - Buffalo Soldiers (The) - annotated outline with notes, 25 Nov 1968 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Buffalo Soldiers (The) - outline, 7 Jan 1969 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Griff
    - Bad Night on the Mountain - annotated story outline, 5 Nov 1973 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      Writers: Harkins, John
    - Countdown to Terror - production information and credit sheet, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Elephant in a Cage - production information, cast list, and credit sheet, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Fugitive From Fear - production information, cast sheets, and shooting schedules, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Fugitive From Fear - script, 23 Nov 1973 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Fugitive From Fear - script, 29 Nov 1973 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Writers: Fischer, Peter S.
    - Hammerlock - production information, cast sheets, and shooting schedules, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Hammerlock - script, 9 Nov 1973 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Writers: Maschler, Tim; Nelson, Dick
    - Hammerlock - script, 7 Nov 1973 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Her Name Was Nancy - production information, cast sheets, and shooting schedules, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Her Name Was Nancy- annotated script, 31 Oct 1973 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Incoming memos, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 69)
      Memos include ASI test results for "All the Lonely People" and program schedule.
    - Isolate and Destroy - annotated script, 16 Nov 1973 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      Writers: Driskill, William
    - Isolate and Destroy - production information, cast sheets, shooting schedules, and story outline, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Isolate and Destroy - script, 20 Nov 1973 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Last Ballad (The) - production information and credit sheet, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Legacy of Death - annotated script, 5 Nov 1973 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      Writers: Hamner, Robert
    - Legacy of Death - script, 15 Nov 1973 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Loose Programming information material, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Publicity information bulletins, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - Sudden Passing of Aldo Karabian (The) - production information and shooting schedule, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Heroes (The)
    - Heroes (The) - outline, 21 Oct 1968 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      Writers: Law, Warner
  - Holly Golightly
    - Holly Golightly - annotated outline (and one clean copy), 26 Jul 1968 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      Writers: Henerson, James
    - Holly Golightly - annotated script, 18 Oct 1968 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Holly Golightly - annotated script, 18 Oct 1968 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Holly Golightly - annotated script (and one clean copy) with notes attached, 20 Aug 1968 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Holly Golightly - annotated teaser script fragments, 4 Nov 1968 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Holly Golightly - outline and production information, no date (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Holly Golightly - script, 10 Sep 1968 (2 copies) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Immortal (The)
    - Immortal (The) - outline, no date (Box 14, Folder 5)
      Writers: Specht, Robert
    - Immortal (The) - outline, 22 Nov 1968 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - In Name Only
    - In Name Only - annotated script, 8 Nov 1968 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      Writers: Slade, Bernard
    - In Name Only - outline (2 copies), May, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - In Name Only - productioniinformation, and broadcast standards, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Keep and Eye on Denise
    - Keep and Eye on Denise - annotated outline, 20 Jun 1968 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      Writers: Roberts, Stanley
    - Keep and Eye on Denise - annotated script, 1 Oct 1968 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Keep and Eye on Denise - annotated script, 1 Oct 1968 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Keep and Eye on Denise - annotated script, 1 Oct 1968 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Keep and Eye on Denise - outline, 20 Jun 1968 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Keep and Eye on Denise - productioniinformation, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Keep and Eye on Denise - script, 1 Oct 1968 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Mr. Deeds Goes to Town
    - Mr. Deeds Goes to Town - annotated script, 1 Jul 1968 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Mr. Deeds Goes to Town - annotated script, 11 Mar 1968 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Mr. Deeds Goes to Town - annotated script, 1 Jul 1968 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Mr. Deeds Goes to Town - annotated script, 22 Aug 1968 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Mr. Deeds Goes to Town - annotated script, 11 Oct 1968 (Box 15, Folder 17)